[{"answer": "Mom, I wanted you to be the first to know that Tom has asked me to marry him", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Oh, how wonderful!  You are engaged", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Mom, I wanted you to be the first to know that Tom has asked me to marry him", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yes, he proposed over dinner last night", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Oh, how wonderful!  You are engaged", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Did he give you a ring", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Yes, he proposed over dinner last night", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Yes, a simple but beautiful diamond", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Did he give you a ring", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " How lovelyShould we have an engagement party to announce it to everyone", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Yes, a simple but beautiful diamond", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " That would be nice. Maybe we can have family and friends over this weekend fo", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " How lovelyShould we have an engagement party to announce it to everyone", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " GreatI would be happy to cook", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 24, "question": " That would be nice. Maybe we can have family and friends over this weekend fo", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Tom and I did talk about a date for the wedding, June 10th", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 25, "question": " GreatI would be happy to cook", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " A June wedding. Wonderful", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Tom and I did talk about a date for the wedding, June 10th", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yes, we have to go to the courthouse and apply for the license, right", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 30, "question": " A June wedding. Wonderful", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Yes, the county courthouse in the city. And the cost is about $25 and you nee", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Yes, we have to go to the courthouse and apply for the license, right", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " I think blood tests are required also to get the license", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yes, the county courthouse in the city. And the cost is about $25 and you nee", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " In this state of Connecticut, you have to have blood tests. Most states do no", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 36, "question": " I think blood tests are required also to get the license", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " I think when you apply for the license, you must get married within 65 days, or th", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 38, "question": " In this state of Connecticut, you have to have blood tests. Most states do no", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 44, "question": " I think when you apply for the license, you must get married within 65 days, or th", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Yes, and the license must also be signed by the person who conducted th", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Yes, and that person has to be certified by the state to perform marriag", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Yes, and the license must also be signed by the person who conducted th", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Actually, Toms cousin is a pastor and he can perform the wedding ceremony", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yes, and that person has to be certified by the state to perform marriag", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Great.  Have you thought of where you want the wedding ceremony to tak", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Actually, Toms cousin is a pastor and he can perform the wedding ceremony", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Well, Toms brother works at a very nice hotel downtown. So, we thought we coul", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Great.  Have you thought of where you want the wedding ceremony to tak", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Fabulous idea", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Well, Toms brother works at a very nice hotel downtown. So, we thought we coul", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I know some people get married in a church and then drive to the reception at ", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Fabulous idea", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Good ideaI know you probably havent had time to think of color", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 68, "question": " I know some people get married in a church and then drive to the reception at ", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " I have. I think ivory and purple colorswhat do you think", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Good ideaI know you probably havent had time to think of color", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " The ivory for your wedding dress, and the purple for the color of th", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 70, "question": " I have. I think ivory and purple colorswhat do you think", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Michele and Rosie. And Linda, my sister, will be my maid of honor", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 73, "question": " The ivory for your wedding dress, and the purple for the color of th", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Beautiful! Who is the best man", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Michele and Rosie. And Linda, my sister, will be my maid of honor", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Toms brother, Mike", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Beautiful! Who is the best man", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Where do you think you want to honeymoon", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Toms brother, Mike", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " So many place", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Where do you think you want to honeymoon", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Where would Tom like to go", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 81, "question": " So many place", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Well, we would like to go to Italy. But that would be expensive", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Where would Tom like to go", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " How about San Francisco? I know you have never been there and you alway", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Well, we would like to go to Italy. But that would be expensive", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Thats a good ideaand it may not be that expensive. And Tom has never see", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " How about San Francisco? I know you have never been there and you alway", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " There are so many things to see in San Franciscothe Golden Gat", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thats a good ideaand it may not be that expensive. And Tom has never see", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " That would be nice", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 95, "question": " There are so many things to see in San Franciscothe Golden Gat", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Anyplace will be if it is your honeymoon", "docId": "07-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " That would be nice", "qSentId": 95}]
